                Ohm; call and complete Elana s m 
                to = Michael. B = Eta.,
  A Hello. Michael Kennedy.                  Mce
  B I     Michael.  Elana
  A Hello. Flans. how are you?               nat
  B I'm fine. thank you And you?
  A Wry well. thanks What can I do for you?  Tim
  B I'd like to arrange a meeting with sou
  A OK. no problem ..                        71 
  B It's about the plans fot the new employees'
   training week                             Ra
  A Fine. When shall we meet?
  B One day next week?
  A OK How about Tuesday in the afternoon? That s 
   the 15th.
  B No. I'm afraid I'm busy all day on Tuesday. What 
   about Thursday or Friday?
  A Som. I cant make Friday. I'm on a course. But 
  Thursday is fine. Morning or afternoon?
  B The afternoon is best for me.
  A OK. Shall we say 2.30?
  B Yes. that's line. Where shall we meet?
  A You've got a bigger office!
  B OK. So that's half past two on Thursday rth 
  August. in my office.
A Right.
B Thanks. Michael. I'll look forward to seeing you 
  then.

  Exercise 7 I    Read the call again. Find and ung1 
                  more phrases which:
                  I say you want a meeting
                  2 explain the reason for the meet
                  3 suggest a day Of time
                  4 agree to a day or time

